ACTWU's Social Services Department Records 5619/023
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Affirmative Action Plans, 1976-1978 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Affirmative Action Foreign Experience, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Communication Services Department Information, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union - Greenville, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Annual Statistics, 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Aging, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Agency Newsletter, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Alcoholism, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Anderson Social Services Resource List (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Board of Trustees, United Labor Service Agency, 1979-1981 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Community Service Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Combined Federal Campaign Funds, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Crime and Delinquency, 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Child Support Enforcement Program, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Communication Workers of America Training Session, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Emergency Assistance Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Football, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  22 photographs
- Funding Sources, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- General Correspondence, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Health Fair Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Hill Burton Act, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Hypertension, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Housing - Low income Housing and Apartments available (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Guest Book, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Humanities, 1980-1981 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Labor Dispute Information (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Legal Services, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Mailing List Client (Box 42, Folder 5)
- National Association of Social Workers Mailing List, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Fair Labor Standards Act (Minimum Wage Information), 1977-1980 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Mailing List Board (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Medicaid Information, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Churches (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Monthly Reports, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Labor Unity Supper, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Annual Report, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Newsletters, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Occupational Safety and Health act (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Public Service Announcements, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Press Releases, 1978-1980 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Publicity, 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Program Materials and Information, 1977-1979 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Labor Services Agency Report to Local Unions, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Resource File, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Red Cross, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Release Forms (Box 42, Folder 24)
- South Carolina State - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1977-1980 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Sexual Harassment, 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- Social Readjustment Scale (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Spartanburg Agencies and Resources, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Strike Assistance, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 29)
- Social Security Information, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 30)
- Southerners for Economic Justice, 1978-1980 (Box 42, Folder 31)
- Telephone Logs, 1978-1980 (Box 42, Folder 32)
- Trade Readjustment Act, 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 33)
- Unemployment Information, 1979-1981 (Box 42, Folder 34)
- Workers Institute for Safety and Health, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 35)
- Workmen's Compensation, 1978-1980 (Box 42, Folder 36)
- Job Match, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 37)
- Job Match/Notes on Finances, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 38)
- Job Match: General Correspondence, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 39)
- Job Match: General Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 40)
- Job Match: General Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 42, Folder 41)
- Job Match: 2nd Year Proposal, 1983-1986 (Box 42, Folder 42)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers: Job Match, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 43)
- Returned Word Processing Forms, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 44)
- Jobmatch Project, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  August 8; Spanish and English
- Jobmatch: Contract with Cornell University Research Foundation, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 46)
- Daily Reminder, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Jobmatch Second Year Proposal, 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Proposal (Final) Original Document, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Proposal: Original Document, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Proposal Guidelines, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Survey of Joint Boards, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Jobmatch: New York Joint Board, 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Cavalier Uniforms: New York Joint Board, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Dell Clothing: New York Joint Board, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Canaan Fashions: New York Joint Board, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Universal: New York Joint Board, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- New York Joint Board: Manhattan Coats, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Catania Clothing Corporation 85 5th Avenue, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Jobmatch: #4 Cutters, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Jobmatch: #169, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- New York: New York City #169; J.Y.A.F. Queens; Retraining, 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Messages for Brian Foster, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Trylon Shirt and Leis, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Jobmatch: Neckwear, 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Christian Dior (Hathaway), 1985 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Dunleigh-Tuxton: Neckwear Joint Board, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Berkley Ties, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- King's Choice (Neckwear), 1985 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Jobmatch: Amalgamated Services and Allied Industries, 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Riteway Laundry co. Allied Inc., 1985 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Jobmatch: #2 Capmakers, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Sam Bonk Uniforms: #2H, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Benkel Caps (2H) (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Myrna Novelties 555 Broadway, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- New Jersey Goldstar Hat and Cap, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 30)
- Local--102 and Headwear and Allied Workers Joint Board, 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- (Headwear) Nik Togs, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 32)
- Jobmatch: Greater New York Joint Board (Textile) (Box 43, Folder 33)
- Jobmatch: Headwear Joint Board, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 34)
- Jobmatch: #340 Retail, 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 35)
- Jobmatch: #340A Retail, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 36)
- Xerox Log, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 37)
- Word Processing Log, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 38)
- Joint Training and Research (JTR) Materials, 1975-1981 (Box 43, Folder 39)
- Jobmatch: Program Coordinator, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 40)
- Jobmatch: Student Assignment, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 41)
- Jobmatch: Calenders, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 42)
- Newsletter: Original Copies, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 43)
- Threads Newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 44)
- Mature Women, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 45)
- Address Labels, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 46)
- Medical Review, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 47)
- Medicare, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 48)
- Members' Benefit Program, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 49)
- Correspondence: Members, 1972-1977 (Box 43, Folder 50)
- Menninger Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 51)
- Mental Health, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 52)
- Ruth Messinger, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 53)
- Metric B.D. - Labor (Box 43, Folder 54)
- Metric Board - Personnel, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 55)
- Metric Board Procedures, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 56)
- Metric Council, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 57)
- Mexico, 1980-1991 (Box 43, Folder 58)
- Mexico Fair Trade Agreement, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 59)
- Mexico - Sindicato National, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 60)
  June 24
- Michigan State AFL-CIO, 1981-1987 (Box 43, Folder 61)
- Mid-life Industrial Rehab Handicapped - Illinois, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 62)
- Middle East, 1990-1992 (Box 43, Folder 63)
- Midwest Academy, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 64)
- Midwest Regional Conference, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 65)
- Medicaid (Box 43, Folder 66)
- Jobmatch: Shirt and Leisurewear, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 67)
- Stetson for Ladies: Headwear, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 68)
- Midwest Regional News, 1964-1993 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Midwest School, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Migrant workers, 1972-1990 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Mine Workers, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Minimum Wage, 1977-1992 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Minimum Wage - Women, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Walter Mondale Campaign, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Moscow, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Moynihan Bill, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Multinationals, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1972-1989 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- The National Assembly, 1978-1980 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- National Academy of Social Insurance, 1988-1991 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- National Advisors Committee for Women [1 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- National Advisory Committee on Women [2 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Worker's Union - Disaster Relief Fund, 1990-1995 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Cornell/ILR Bachrach Study, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- New Jersey Dyers' Strike, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union - Social Services, 1986-1992 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union - Social Services, 1987-1992 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Keiltext Corporation, Keiltronics Incorporated, Keilson Ind. Charlotte, North Carolina, 1989-1991 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Glove Cities, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Midwest Flood, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Worker's Union - Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union - Social Services Department Mission Statement, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Conway Company, "Garment Center Real Estate Analysis", 1986 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, Papers, 1988-2001 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Drug Testing, 1987-1993 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Employee Assistance Program, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1990-1992 (Box 44, Folder 31)
- Employee Assistance Program (EPA), General, 1986-1988 (Box 44, Folder 32)
- Employee Assistance Program, Local 2269, Johnson and Johnson. Skillman, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 33)
- Emanuel Weintraub Associates. "Survey Results Garment Center - SIC 233, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 34)
- Fact Sheets and Work Shops, 1990-1999 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Garfield Schwartz Associates "Feasibility of Relocating the Garment Industry to the Brooklyn Army Terminal", 1983 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- History, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (Box 45, Folder 3)
- History, Labor, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- History Male Apparel Industry (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Human Services Programs, 1977-1981 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Members Assistance Program (Map). Return to Work (RTW) Conference (Box 45, Folder 7)
- New York City United Way, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Program for Unemployed Members, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Staff Assistance Program, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Social Services Department Programs, 1978-1982 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- "Summary of the Census: New York City's Garment Center,", 1985 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Training Manual Excerpts (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Training Manual for Members of Social Services Committees of Local Unions (Box 45, Folder 14)
- UNITE: Sweatshop Campaign, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Work and Family Life Project. Antoniades, Ruth; Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Work and Family Life Project. Margolis, Lewis H. and Dale C. Farram. "Health and Behavioral Consequences for Children of Parental Job Loss", 1981 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Work and Family Life Project, Interview Guide, 1981-1983 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Work and Family Life Project. Articles, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Workshop, Managing Stress Effectively (Box 45, Folder 20)
- United Labor Services Agency Flyers (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Social Services - Contact Records, 1978-1981 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  loose 5 by 8 inch cards
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Worker's Union: Zaperteros Unidos Mision:Empleo, Contact Cards, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  Loose 3 by 5 inch cards
- Official Union Contact Cards for South Carolina (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Social Services Contact Cards (Box 46, Folder 3)